bestsavingsdaily.com 2016-01-25

# BestSavingsDaily.com | Best Savings In Life.

This privacy policy (Privacy Policy) herein contains information of our practices and policies regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you submit to BestSavingsDaily and through our website www.bestsavingsdaily.com. 

### **Collection of personal information**

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual. When you browse our website, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously indicated that you wish bestsavingsdaily.com to remember your login and password. Bestsavingsdaily.com does log your IP address to give us an idea of which part of our website you visited and how long you spend there. Unless you request your personal information to be deleted, it will be retained by BestSavingsDaily.com to verify compliance, track software and page visits on our site. We may use and/or receive personal information from third party partners, but only use such information if it has been obtained in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with its policy and applicable laws. 

### **Non Personal Information**

This is the type of information that does not directly identify a user on the site. This information can include the type of browser used, the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) used in the query and other elements such as your IP address. BestSavingsDaily.com as well as our third party partners may collect this information directly or through pixels and/or cookies placed on this site. We use this information to conform and cooperate with local and Federal laws and law enforcement. The right to share this information with Third Party service providers and advertisers is reserved by BestSavingsDaily.com in the effort to quantify our advertising efforts. 

### **Information You Provide**

This site collects information automatically provided to us from your browser. This includes your IP address and URL. Additionally this site uses Cookies to store information on uses, who visit the site, and allows your information to be stored for future use within the site. Information you provide on partner sites or third party sites are beholden to the agreements with those sites, and not BestSavingsDaily.com. By knowingly providing any information to a third party or partner on this site you are opting in for that company or partner to use that information, this includes contacting you at the email or phone number that you provided for existing and future sales, promotions and marketing. 

### **Collection of Email**

Consumers may opt to provide their email address to bestsavingsdaily.com with the expectation that they will be contacted by bestsavingsdaily.com. BestSavingsDaily.com uses this email address for internal marketing purposes only, and the emails that are collected on partner sites is information collected for the use of that offer only. 

### **Business Relationships**

During your experience with BestSavingsDaily.com you may encounter third party advertisers who work with us to provide offers and services to you online. BestSavingsDaily.com does not control the information, products or services available on these third party websites. While this company works with third party advertisers it does not have control over the information, products or services available on these websites. Any dealings with, or participation in promotions offered by third party advertisers on the website are solely the dealings of you and the advertiser in question. You also agree that the Company shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any loss or damage caused by the use of or reliance on any such material made available with a third party advertiser. 

### **Telephone Consumer Protection Act**

According to the Telephone Consumer Protection ACT (TCPA) if you submit a phone number on this site you are agreeing to receive calls to that number. This is not a condition of confirmation to buy or receive goods and/or services. 

### **No information Collected From Children**

This site will never knowingly collect the information of any individual under the age of 18. 

### **Indemnification**

You agree to hold this company, its parents and subsidiaries and all respective members harmless from and against any and all claims, expenses (including attorney fees to a reasonable extent), damages, suits, costs, demands and/or judgement made by a third party due to your use of the website, your breach of this agreement, or your violation of any rights of any other individuals and/or entities. 

### **Warranties**

This website and the products featured on it are provided to you Ã¢â‚¬Å“as isÃ¢â‚¬Â. All warranties, both explicit and implicit, are disclaimed to the fullest extent permissible to any applicable law. This includes that that the website makes no warranty or guarantee that the products or services will do the following: Meet your requirements, be error free or be corrected of any errors, be free of harmful components, will result in any health-related or financial-related outcome, or be accurate and/or reliable. The company is not liable for the availability of online connections or the impact it may have on your experience.
